hyenacart.com 2019-07-08

# Privacy Policy :: Hyena Cart

This privacy policy exists to let you know what information you provide to Hyena Cart is collected, and how this information is used and shared. Privacy is very important to us at Hyena Cart and you should know up-front that none of your information will be shared with third-parties, nor will you receive unsolicited email from Hyena Cart as a result of account registration. 

Please review this policy frequently as it may change in the future. 

_**Account Registration**_

At the time of account registration, your first name and email address will be collected and stored. Your first name is used in greeting messages throughout the site to make you feel welcome. Your name and email address are provided to sellers from whom you place orders so that they can communicate with you and ensure a satisfactorily completed transaction. 

Upon registration, an activation email will be sent to you to confirm your email address. In addition, you may request password resets which will be sent to you via email. 

Registration to the Hyena Cart Forums includes optional information such as url, and alternate contact methods. This information is purely voluntary and can be shared by you at will. The forum software will also send notification emails of private messages and post notifications if you choose to receive them. 

_**Orders**_

When you complete a transaction through a Hyena Cart store, if it is completed via Paypal, your full name and address will be stored within the Hyena Cart database as a reference to the seller. This information is available only to the seller with whom the transaction was completed and will not be shared with anyone else. 

_**Polls and Surveys**_

Occasionally, polls or surveys may be conducted to determine and prioritize needed Hyena Cart features. These polls will be conducted on-line, with no email, and the individual results will be kept strictly confidential. Statistical and aggregate information from these polls will be shared in a non-personally identifiable manner. 

_**Communications from the Site**_

Aside from the aforementioned registration confirmation emails, passwords resets, and forum notifications, the only email that will be sent to you by Hyena Cart are purchase and payment notifications during transactions. Hyena Cart will not send promotional, service-related or information emails of any kind. If you wish to stay abreast of the latest Hyena Cart news, you may request email notification from the HC Blog. You can also request to be removed from this mailing list at any time. 

_**Automatic Collection of Information**_

_Cookies_

A cookie is a small text file that is stores on your computer for record-keeping purposes. Session ID cookies are used to enhance your navigation of the Hyena Cart site. These cookies expire when you close your browser. In addition, persistent cookies may be used (per your choice) to store your log in information to prevent the need to re-enter your log-in information when returning to the site. Cookies are used to track traffic in various stores, identify you when making purchases and spotting items as well as posting in the forums. 

You may choose to reject cookies, but this will limit your ability to use the Hyena Cart site. 

_IP Addresses_

IP addresses are collected at login, during purchasing, item spotting, and posting in the HC Forums. These addresses are used to trace fraudulent posts or purchases, and to prevent multiple spotting of the same item from the same IP. IP addresses are also used to track traffic around the site, most notably for the "Where are the Hyenas?" list. 

_Log files_

We use a third-party tracking service called Statcounter.com that uses log files to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to Hyena cart. This information is used in volume statistics to analyze trends and administer the site. 

_**Advertising**_

The ads appearing on Hyena Cart are provided through Hyena Cart itself. Click-through statistics are provided to advertisers in a form which is not personally identifiable. 

_**Links to other Sites**_

This web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Hyena Cart. Please be aware, that we, Hyena Cart, are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. 

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this web site. 

_**Forums**_

If you use a bulletin board or chat room on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. 

_**Changing account preferences**_

You may change your email, address, password and first name anytime using the "My HC" link. If you wish to combine accounts, there is a link to do that as well. 

To delete your account, please contact Customer Support at [support@hyenacart.com](emailto:support@hyenacart.com). 

_**Business Transitions**_

In the event Hyena Cart goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

_**Changes in this Privacy Statement**_

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here or by means of a notice on our home page. 

_**Contact Us**_

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [support@hyenacart.com](emailto:support@hyenacart.com).
